Register of the Russia Missiia (Greece) Records, 1874-1925
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1874-1924
  - Gadzhemukov family
    - 1907 (Folder 16)
    - 1907? (Folder 17)
    - 1910 (Folder 18)
    - 1911 (Folder 19)
    - 1912 (Folder 20)
    - 1913 (Folder 21)
    - 1913? (Folder 22)
    - 1914 (Folder 23)
    - 1914? (Box 33., Folder 1)
    - 1915 (Folder 2)
  - Geandre, C. & Co. (Folder 3)
  - Greece
    - Athenaike Lesche. Report, 1920 (Folder 4)
    - Constantine, King
      - Assassination (Folder 5)
      - Associated Press (Folder 6)
    - Debts (Folder 7)
    - Diplomatic and consular service in
      - General
        - 1911 (Folder 8)
        - 1918 (Folder 9)
        - 1922-1923 (Folder 10)
      - Military agents. See Registry Commission of Korinthos
      - Registry Commission of Korinthos (Folder 11)
      - Russian mission and consulates, Government credits to the. See also SUBJECT FILE/Greece/Telegraph
        - 1918
          - June (Folder 12)
          - September-December (Folder 13)
        - 1919
          - January-April (Folder 14)
          - May-June (Folder 15)
          - July-September (Folder 16)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 17)
      - Special Consular Commission in Chania
        - General (Folder 18)
        - Printed matter (Folder 19)
    - Foreign relations. See also Diplomatic and consular service in
      - General
        - n.d. (Folder 20)
        - 1915 (Folder 21)
        - 1916 (Folder 22)
        - 1916-1917 (Folder 23)
        - 1917 (Box 34., Folder 1)
        - 1918 (Folder 2)
      - Blockade of Greece, 1917 (Folder 3)
      - Bulgaria (Folder 4)
      - German intelligence service. See Germany
      - Germany (Folder 5)
      - Great Britain (Folder 6)
      - High Commission of Guarantor Powers, 1917 (Folder 7)
      - Italy (Folder 8)
      - Romania (Folder 9)
      - Turkey
        - 1910 (Folder 10)
        - 1917 (Folder 11)
        - 1921 (Folder 12)
      - Ultimatum by the Allied powers, 1917 (Folder 13)
      - USSR
        - General
          - 1916-1917 (Folder 14)
          - 1920-1924 (Folder 15)
        - Commerce. See also SUBJECT FILE/Commerce
          - General (Folder 16)
          - Press comments (Folder 17)
    - Foreigners -- abolition of privileges (Folder 18)
    - Government and politics. See also Foreign relations; and Law and legislation; and SUBJECT FILE/ Awards and decorations
      - General
        - 1916? (Folder 19)
        - 1917
          - General (Folder 20)
          - Venizelos (Folder 21)
          - Zaimis (Folder 22)
        - 1919 (Folder 23)
        - 1920 (Box 35., Folder 1)
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 2)
        - 1922 (Folder 3)
        - 1922-1923 (Folder 4)
        - 1923-1924 (Folder 5)
      - Crete question, 1911 (Folder 6)
      - Military League, 1909-1910 (Folder 7)
      - Military rising in Macedonia, 1923 (Folder 8)
      - Ministry of Foreign Affairs (Folder 9)
      - Northern Epirus (Folder 10)
      - Provisional government, Thessalonike, 1916-1917 (Box 36., Folder 1)
    - George I, King, Assassination of (Folder 2)
    - Greek National Bank
      - n.d. (Folder 3)
      - 1915 (Folder 4)
      - 1916 (Folder 5)
      - 1917 (Folder 6)
      - 1923 (Folder 7)
    - Greek Socialist (Communist) Workers Party (Folder 8)
    - Ionian Bank (Folder 9)
    - Kauffman library (Folder 10)
    - Laws and legislation
      - 1911 (Folder 11)
      - 1912. See also 1919 (Folder 12)
      - 1914 (Folder 13)
      - 1917 (Folder 14)
      - 1919
        - New Agrarian Law (Folder 15)
        - Vogazle, D.K., Agrotike kai epoikistike nomothesia (Agrarian and Settlement Legislation), 1912-1919. Athens, 1919 (Folder 16)
      - 1922 (Folder 17)
      - 1923 (Folder 18)
    - Left wing movements. See Foreign relations/USSR
    - Press
      - General
        - n.d. (Box 37., Folder 1)
        - 1916 (Folder 2)
        - 1916-1917 (Folder 3)
        - 1917 (Folder 4)
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 5)
        - 1920 (Folder 6)
      - Censorship (Folder 7)
      - Propaganda (Folder 8)
      - Romanov dynasty --300th Anniversary. Clippings (Folder 9)
    - Royal household and court
      - General
        - 1915-1919 (Box 38., Folder 1)
        - 1918 (Folder 2)
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 3)
        - 1921 (Folder 4)
        - 1922-1923 (Folder 5)
      - Clippings (Folder 6-10)
    - Telegraph
      - n.d. (Box 39., Folder 1)
      - 1905 (Folder 2)
      - 1913 (Folder 3)
      - 1915 (Folder 4)
      - 1916 (Folder 5)
      - 1916-1917 (Folder 6)
      - 1917 (Folder 7)
      - 1918 (Folder 8)
      - 1919 (Folder 9)
      - 1920 (Folder 10)
      - 1921 (Folder 11)
      - 1922 (Folder 12)
      - 1923 (Folder 13)
      - 1924 (Folder 14)
  - Greek church. See Orthodox Eastern Church
  - Greek nationals. See Personnel/Greek nationals
  - Greek schools -- Donations by the Russian Imperial Government (Box 40., Folder 1)
  - Greeks in foreign countries. See also Russian diplomatic and consular service/Ethiopia; and USSR/Revolution/ Counterrevolutionary movements/South/Denikin/Greek colony (Folder 2)
  - Hague Peace Conference, 1907 (Folder 3)
  - International Financial Commission. See also Greece/ Greek National Bank
    - 1913 (Folder 4)
    - 1914-1920 (Folder 5)
    - 1916-1918 (Folder 6)
    - 1921-1923 (Folder 7)
  - Italo-Turkish War, 1911 (Folder 8)
  - Kamba, Semen (Folder 9)
  - Khadzhas, Georgii. See Kamba
  - Korbe, Mikhail (Folder 10)
  - Latvia. See Baltic states
  - Left wing movements. See Extradition; and Switzerland -- left wing propaganda
  - Literature
    - Criticism -- Conference on Ivan Turgenev (Folder 11)
    - Drama (Folder 12-14)
    - Turgenev, Ivan. See Criticism -- Conference on Ivan Turgenev
  - Lithuania. See Baltic states
  - Lukull, Yacht (Folder 15)
  - Mansurov, Edigei (Folder 16)
  - Middle East -- Political conditions, 1918-1919 (Folder 17)
  - Navarino naval battle --200th Anniversary (Folder 18)
  - Orthodox Eastern church. See also RUSSIAN CHURCH
    - Anglican church, Relations with (Folder 19)
    - Ecumenical Patriarch, Jerusalem
      - 1907 (Folder 20)
      - 1915 (Folder 21)
      - 1917 (Folder 22)
      - 1918 (Folder 23)
      - 1919 (Folder 24)
      - 1920 (Box 41., Folder 1)
      - 1921 (Folder 2)
      - 1922 (Folder 3)
      - 1923 (Folder 4)
      - 1924 (Folder 5)
    - Meletius, Metropolitan of Athens. See also Patriarch of Constantinople (Folder 6)
    - Monasteries in Epirus (Folder 7)
    - Patriarch of Constantinople (Folder 8)
  - Panagiotato, Aglaia (Folder 9)
  - Panhellenism (Folder 10)
  - Papparigopoulo (Folder 11)
  - Paris, Conference of, 1919-1920 (Folder 12)
  - Paris Sanitary Convention (Folder 13)
  - Pavanna, Freighter (Folder 14)
  - Personnel. See also Awards and decorations
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 15)
      - 1873 (Folder 16)
      - 1906 (Folder 17)
      - 1914 (Folder 18)
      - 1915 (Folder 19)
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 20)
      - 1916 (Folder 21)
      - 1917 (Folder 22)
      - 1918 (Folder 23)
      - 1919 (Folder 24)
      - 1919-1921 (Folder 25)
      - 1922-1923 (Folder 26)
    - Books and office supply (Box 42., Folder 1)
    - Cars (Folder 2)
    - Chekmarev (Folder 3)
    - Coal (Folder 4)
    - Demidov, Elim
      - 1915? (Folder 5)
      - 1917 (Folder 6)
      - 1917-1918 (Folder 7)
      - 1919 (Folder 8)
      - 1920 (Folder 9)
      - 1922 (Folder 10)
      - 1923 (Folder 11)
    - Demidova, Sof'ia (Folder 12)
    - Extraordinary payments (Folder 13)
    - Food supplies
      - General (Folder 14)
      - Bread (Folder 15)
    - Garshin, Mikhail (Folder 16)
    - Grammatopulo
      - Greek government and politics. See World politics
      - Orthodox Eastern Church. See World politics
      - Salaries (Folder 17)
      - World politics. Reports
        - n.d. (Folder 18)
        - 1918
          - January-June (Folder 19)
          - July (Folder 20)
          - August (Folder 21)
          - September (Folder 22)
          - October (Folder 23)
          - November (Folder 24)
          - December (Folder 25)
        - 1919
          - January (Folder 26)
          - February (Folder 27)
          - March (Box 43., Folder 1)
          - April (Folder 2)
          - May (Folder 3)
          - June (Folder 4)
          - July (Folder 5)
          - August (Folder 6)
          - September (Folder 7)
          - October (Folder 8)
          - November (Folder 9)
          - December (Folder 10)
        - 1920
          - January-February (Folder 11)
          - March (Folder 12)
          - April (Folder 13)
          - May (Folder 14)
          - June (Folder 15)
          - July (Folder 16)
          - August (Folder 17)
          - September (Folder 18)
          - October (Folder 19)
          - November (Folder 20)
          - December (Folder 21)
        - 1921
          - January (Folder 22)
          - February (Folder 23)
          - March (Folder 24)
          - April (Folder 25)
          - May (Folder 26)
          - June (Folder 27)
          - July (Folder 28)
          - August (Folder 29)
          - September (Folder 30)
          - October (Folder 31)
          - November (Folder 32)
          - December (Folder 33)
        - 1922
          - January (Box 44., Folder 1)
          - February (Folder 2)
          - March (Folder 3)
          - April (Folder 4)
          - May (Folder 5)
          - June (Folder 6)
          - July (Folder 7)
          - September (Folder 8)
          - December (Folder 9)
        - 1923
          - January (Folder 10)
          - February (Folder 11)
          - March (Folder 12)
          - June-December (Folder 13)
        - 1924 (Folder 14)
    - Greek nationals, including those who were not in the service of the Russian Government
      - General
        - 1916 (Folder 15)
        - 1917 (Folder 16)
        - 1918 (Folder 17)
        - 1919 (Folder 18)
        - 1921 (Folder 19)
        - 1922-1923 (Folder 20)
      - Alogopulo (Folder 21)
      - Anamissaki (Folder 22)
      - Khristidis, Khristo (Folder 23)
      - Kongoianaki (Folder 24)
      - Letiurgidis (Folder 25)
      - Sharl'ton, Karl (Folder 26)
      - Volanis, Nikifor (Folder 27)
    - IAkushev, Boris
      - 1915 (Folder 28)
      - 1916 (Folder 29)
      - 1916-1917
        - Diplomatic mail pouch (Folder 30)
        - Grant (Folder 31)
      - 1919 (Folder 32)
      - 1922 (Folder 33)
    - Ikskul'-Gillenberg, Aleksei, Baron
      - 1916 (Folder 34)
      - 1917? (Folder 35)
    - Lerkhe (Box 45., Folder 1)
    - Mavromati. See IAkushev, Boris/ 1916-1917
    - Omel'chenko (Folder 2)
    - Papavasiliu. See Omel'chenko
    - Pensions (Folder 3)
    - Salaries
      - 1915 (Folder 4)
      - 1916 (Folder 5)
      - 1917 (Folder 6)
    - Shpadierg, Marko (Folder 7)
    - Shtrandtman (Folder 8)
    - Sukin. See also Iakushev, Boris/ 1917 (Folder 9)
    - Urusov, S.L., Prince (Folder 10)
    - Van der Giukht (Folder 11)
    - Voenno-morskoi agent (Naval Agent). See also SUBJECT FILE/Geandre, C. & Co.
      - Makalinskii, A. (Folder 12)
      - Zubruzhitskii, Vladimir (Folder 13)
    - Voennyi agent (Military Agent)
      - Gudim-Levkovich
        - 1915-1916 (Folder 14)
        - 1916-1917 (Folder 15)
      - Gul'tiaev, Makar, Servant (Folder 16)
      - Leont'ev (Folder 17)
      - Mukhanov. See also Leont'ev (Folder 18)
      - Nevadovskii (Folder 19)
      - Poliakov. See also Vil'chkovskii (Folder 20)
      - Vil'chkovskii, Assistant (Folder 21)
  - Polymitis, Freighter (Folder 22)
  - Red Cross societies of the Allied countries, 1916-1917 (Folder 23)
  - Russian bank notes (Folder 24)
  - Russian diplomatic and consular service. See also USSR/ Ministerstvo inostrannykh del; and RUSSIAN CONSULATES IN GREECE AND TURKEY
    - Composition and structure (Folder 25)
    - Conference of Russian representatives abroad, Paris, 1919 (Folder 26)
    - Diplomatic mail pouch (Folder 27)
    - Ethiopia (Folder 28)
    - Great Britain (Box 46., Folder 1)
    - Iran (Folder 2)
    - Italy (Folder 3)
    - Neratov. See Turkey
    - Protopopov. See Italy
    - Romania (Folder 4)
    - Turkey
      - 1909 (Folder 5)
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 6)
  - Russian freighters under foreign flags
    - General (Folder 7)
    - France. See also Greece (Folder 8)
    - Greece. See also SUBJECT FILE/Russko-dunaiskoe parokhodstvo (Folder 9)
  - Russian Navy in Greece (Folder 10)
  - Russkii arkheologicheskii institut (Russian Archeological Institute)
    - Athens (Folder 11)
    - Istanbul. See Athens
  - Russkii dobrovol'nyi flot (Russian Volunteer Fleet) (Folder 12)
  - Russko dunaiskoe parokhodstvo (Russian Danube Steamship Company) (Folder 13)
  - Russkoe obshchestvo parokhodstva i torgovli (Russian Steamship and Trade Society)
    - General (Folder 14)
    - Freighters
      - Odessa (Folder 15)
      - Psezuape (Folder 16)
      - Tigr (Folder 17)
  - Serbia. See Austro-Hungary
  - Sociology -- III International Sociological Congress, Rome, 1923 (Folder 18)
  - Svoboda, Training ship
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 19)
      - 1918 (Folder 20)
      - 1919 (Folder 21)
      - 1919-1922 (Box 47., Folder 1)
    - Receipts
      - 1918 (Folder 2)
      - 1919 (Folder 3)
    - Reports
      - 1918 (Folder 4)
      - 1919 (Folder 5)
  - Switzerland -- Left wing propaganda (Folder 6)
  - USSR
    - Chrezvychainaia sledstvennaia komissiia (Extraordinary Investigation Commission) (Folder 7)
    - Economic and political conditions. See also Foreign relations/Great Britain; and Revolution/ Counterrevolutionary movements/South/Vrangel', Petr/ Biuro russkoi pechati v Konstantinopole and Upravle- nie Glavnoupolnomochennogo Glavnokomanduiushchego Russkoi armii po voennym i morskim delam
      - 1921
        - Korovin (Folder 8)
        - Lenin, Vladimir. (Forged) letter (Folder 9)
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 10)
      - 1922-1923 (Folder 11)
    - Foreign relations
      - General
        - Clippings (Folder 12)
        - Correspondence (Folder 13)
      - Bulgaria (Folder 14)
      - China. See also SUBJECT FILE/USSR/Revolution/ Counterrevolutionary movements/Siberia and Far East/General (Folder 15)
      - Germany (Box 48., Folder 1)
      - Great Britain (Folder 2)
      - India. See SUBJECT FILE/USSR/Revolution/ Counterrevolutionary movements/Siberia and Far East/General
      - Japan. See also China (Folder 3)
      - Norway (Folder 4)
      - United States. See also SUBJECT FILE/Colby, Bainbridge (Folder 5)
      - Vatican (Folder 6)
    - Georgia, Smuggling into (Folder 7)
    - Government loans
      - Liberty, 1917 (Folder 8)
      - War, 1916 (Folder 9)
    - Intelligence service. See SUBJECT FILE/Greece/ Foreign relations/USSR; and SUBJECT FILE/ Russian banknotes
    - Military draft, 1915 (Folder 10)
    - Ministerstvo inostrannykh del (Ministry of Foreign Affairs)
      - Departament lichnogo sostava i khoziaistvennykh del (Personnel, Facilities, and Building Maintenance Department), 1904-1914 (Folder 11)
      - Departament obshchikh del (General Affairs Department) 1917 (Folder 12)
      - Otdel voennoplennykh (Prisoners of War Department)
        - 1916 (Folder 13)
        - 1917 (Folder 14)
      - Pervyi otdel (First Department)
        - 1914 (Folder 15)
        - 1915 (Folder 16)
        - 1916 (Folder 17)
        - 1917 (Folder 18)
      - Pervyi politicheskii otdel (First Political Department), 1916 (Folder 19)
      - Pravovoi departament (Legal Department), 1917 (Folder 20)
      - Vtoroi departament (Second Department), 1916 (Folder 21)
      - Vtoroi politicheskii otdel (Second Political Department), 1916 (Folder 22)
    - Ministerstvo vnutrennikh del (Ministry of Internal Affairs)
      - Departament politsii (Department of Police). Wanted persons' list, 1912-1913 (Folder 23)
      - Upravlenie voinskoi povinnost'iu (Conscription Administration), 1917 (Folder 24)
    - Narodnyi komissariat vnutrennikh del (People's Commissariat of Internal Affairs) (Folder 25)
    - Passports (Folder 26)
    - Revolution, 1917-1921
      - General
        - 1917 (Folder 27)
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 28)
      - Counterrevolutionary movements. See also SUBJECT FILE/Russian diplomatic and consular service/ Turkey/ 1920-1921
        - General
          - 1918 (Box 49., Folder 1)
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 3)
        - Caucasus. See South/Foreign participation
        - North (Folder 4)
        - Siberia and Far East
          - General (Folder 5)
          - All-Russian Government, Omsk
            - General
              - Correspondence
                - 1918 (Folder 6)
                - 1919 (Folder 7)
              - Report -- historical review (Folder 8)
            - Laws and legislation, 1919.
              - Printed matter
                - March-May (Folder 9)
                - June-October (Folder 10)
            - Nachal'nik Otdela Generala kvartir- meistera Voennogo predstavitelia Verkhovnogo pravitelia pri soiuznykh pravitel'stvakh i Komandovanii (Chief of Quarter master Department of Supreme Ruler's Military Representa- tive to the Allied Governments and Command) (Folder 11)
            - Omskoe telegrafnoe agenstvo (Omsk Telegraph Agency) (Folder 12)
          - Semenov, Grigorii (Folder 13)
          - Vladivostok governments (Folder 14)
        - South
          - Denikin
            - General
              - Administrative orders (Folder 15)
              - Correspondence
                - n.d. (Folder 16)
                - 1918 (Folder 17)
                - 1919
                - January-March (Folder 18)
                - April-September (Box 50., Folder 1)
                - 1920 (Folder 2)
              - Reports (Folder 3)
              - Speech, 16 December 1920.
                - Typed copies in
                - French (Folder 4)
                - Russian (Folder 5)
            - Campaigns (Folder 6)
            - Cherniavskii, Nikolai (Folder 7)
            - Greek military mission (Folder 8)
            - Laws and legislation. Printed matter
              - 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
              - 1919
                - January-May (Folder 10)
                - June-August (Folder 11)
            - Osvedomitel'noe agenstvo (Information agency) (Folder 12)
            - Upravlenie inostrannykh del pri Glavnokomanduiushchem vooruzhen- nymi silami na iuge Rossii (Commander-in-Chief of Southern Russia's Armed Forces. Foreign Affairs Administration) (Folder 13)
          - Foreign participation (Folder 14)
          - Greek community (Folder 15)
          - Krymskoe kraevoe pravitel'stvo (Crimean Regional Government) (Folder 16)
          - Vrangel', Petr. See also SUBJECT FILE/ USSR/Foreign relations/Great Britain
            - General
              - Administrative orders (Folder 17)
              - Correspondence
                - General (Folder 18)
                - McCully, N.A. (Folder 19)
            - Biuro russkoi pechati v Konstanti- nopole (Russian Press Bureau, Constantinople) (Box 51., Folder 1)
            - Bogoslovskii, Boris (Folder 2)
            - Campaigns. See also Upravlenie inostrannykh del pri Glavno- komanduiushchem Vooruzhennymi silami na iuge Rossii (Folder 3)
            - Glavnoupolnomochennyi Glavnokoman- duiushchego vooruzhennymi silami iuga Rossii po voennym i morskim delam (Commander-in-Chief's Chief Representative of Southern Russia's Armed Forces on Military and Naval Affairs), Paris (Folder 4)
            - Nachal'nik Voennogo upravleniia Pravitel'stva iuga Rossii (Southern Russian Government's Chief of Military Administra- tion) (Folder 5)
            - Predstavitel' Glanokomanduiu- shchego Vooruzhennymi silami na iuge Rossii pri Soiuznom komandovanii (Commander-in- Chief's Chief Representative of Southern Russia's Armed Forces to the Allied Command), Constantinople (Folder 6)
            - Upravlenie Glavnoupolnomochennogo Glavnokomanduiushchego Russkoi Armii po voennym i morskim delam (Administration of the Commander-in-Chief's Chief Representative on Military and Naval Affairs), Paris. Bulletins (Folder 7)
            - Upravlenie inostrannykh del pri Glavnokomanduiushchem Vooruzhen- nymi silami na iuge Rossii (Commander-in-Chief of Southern Russia's Armed Forces. Administration of Foreign Affairs) (Folder 8)
            - Voennoe predstavitel'stvo Russkoi armii pri soiuznykh pravitel'stvakh i Soiuznom verkhovnom komandovanii (Military Representatives of the Russian Army to the Allied Governments and the Allied High Command), Paris (Folder 9)
        - Ural Mountain (Folder 10)
      - Georgian question. See Ukrainian question/Greece/ Ukrainian delegation in
      - Greek press on the Russian Revolution (Folder 11)
      - Ukrainian question
        - General (Folder 12)
        - All-Ukrainian Church Council (Folder 13)
        - Greece
          - Press (Folder 14)
          - Ukrainian delegation in (Folder 15)
      - Vremennoe pravitel'stvo (Provisional Government). See also USSR/Ministerstvo inostrannykh del (Folder 16)
    - Taxes, 1914 (Folder 17)
  - Urusova, Mariia
    - Account book (Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (Folder 19)
  - Vatican. See Zionism
  - Vil'chitskii. See Discoveries in Arctic region
  - World politics. See USSR/Revolution, 1917-1921/ Counterrevolutionary movements/Siberia and Far East/Nachal'nik Otdela Generala kvartirmeistera Voennogo predstavitelia Verkhovnogo pravitelia pri soiuznykh pravitel'stvakh i Komandovanii; USSR/Revolution/Counterrevolutionary movements/ South/Vrangel', Petr/Biuro russkoi pechati v Konstantinopole and Upravlenie Glavnoupolnomochen- go Glavnokomanduiushchego Russkoi armii po voennym i morskim delam and Upravlenie inostrannykh del pri Glavnokomanduiushchem Vooruzhennymi silami na iuge Rossii; and World War I, 1914-1918
  - World War I, 1914-1918
    - General
      - 1914 (Box 52., Folder 1)
      - 1916
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October (Folder 11)
        - November (Folder 12)
        - December (Box 53., Folder 1)
      - 1917
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October (Folder 11)
        - November (Folder 12)
        - December (Folder 13)
      - 1918 (Folder 14)
    - Athos, Mount. See General/ 1917/January
    - Austro-Hungary. See Germany and Austro-Hungary
    - Bulgaria (Folder 15)
    - Campaigns (Folder 16)
    - Germany (Folder 17)
    - Germany and Austro-Hungary (Box 54., Folder 1)
    - Greece
      - International Military Control
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Cars (Folder 3)
        - Russian officers (Folder 4)
      - Italian troops in Northern Epirus (Folder 5)
      - Russian troops
        - 1916 (Folder 6)
        - 1917 (Folder 7)
        - 1918
          - General (Folder 8)
          - Demidov, Elim, Appeal of (Folder 9)
    - Kurlandia. See Latvia
    - Latvia (Folder 10)
    - Neutral ports (Folder 11)
    - Political cartoons (Folder 12)
    - Prisoners of war in
      - Austro-Hungary. See Germany
      - Bulgaria. See Germany
      - Germany. See also SUBJECT FILE/USSR/Chrez- vychainaia sledstvennaia komissiia and Ministerstvo inostrannykh del/Otdel voennoplen- nykh
        - General (Folder 13)
        - Russian. Questionnaires
          - 1916 (Folder 14)
          - 1917 (Folder 15)
          - 1918 (Folder 16)
      - Russia (Folder 17)
    - Refugees, Serbian (Folder 18)
    - Romania (Folder 19)
    - Submarines. See SUBJECT FILE/Greece/Foreign relations/ Germany
    - Turkey (Folder 20)
    - Washington, Freighter (Folder 21)
  - Yugoslavia (Folder 22)
  - Zifo (Folder 23)